<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="faq_options">
        <item>Intro</item>
        <item>Timeline Summary</item>
        <item>Psyche the Asteroid</item>
        <item>Spacecraft</item>
        <item>Propulsion</item>
        <item>Mission Cost</item>
        <item>Mission Science Goals</item>
        <item>Mission Science Objectives</item>
        <item>Instruments and Investigations</item>
        <item>Psyche Mission Team</item>
        <item>More Information</item>
        <item>References</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="faq_array">
        <item>@string/faq_intro</item>
        <item>@string/faq_timeline_summary</item>
        <item>@string/faq_asteroid</item>
        <item>@string/faq_spacecraft</item>
        <item>@string/faq_propulsion</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_cost</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_science_goals</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_science_objectives</item>
        <item>@string/faq_instruments_and_investigations</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_team</item>
        <item>@string/faq_more_info</item>
        <item>@string/faq_references</item>
    </array>
    <string name="faq_intro">
        "Mission Overview\n\n"
        "•Psyche is:\n"
        "oThe name of an asteroid orbiting the Sun between Mars and Jupiter.\n"
        "oThe name of a NASA space mission to visit that asteroid, led by ASU.\n\n"

        "•Psyche is the first mission to a world made of metal rather than rock or ice.\n\n"

        "•The Psyche mission was chosen by NASA on January 4, 2017.\n\n"

        "•Psyche is the 14th mission selected for NASA’s Discovery Program, a series of "
        "relatively low-cost missions to solar system targets.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_timeline_summary">
        "Summary of Psyche Mission Timeline:\n\n"
        "2022: Launch of Psyche spacecraft from NASA’s Kennedy Space Center, FL\n"
        "2023: Psyche spacecraft flyby of Mars\n"
        "2026: Psyche spacecraft arrives in asteroid’s orbit\n"
        "2026-2027: Psyche spacecraft orbits the Psyche asteroid for 21 months\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_propulsion">
        "Propulsion: Solar-electric (low-thrust) propulsion.\n\n"
        "•Solar electric propulsion uses electricity from solar arrays to create electromagnetic "
        "fields to accelerate and expel charged atoms (ions) of xenon to create a very low thrust "
        "with a very efficient use of propellant[1].\n\n"

        "•This will be the first use of Hall effect thrusters beyond lunar orbit.\n\n"

        "•The Psyche spacecraft is using xenon:\n\n"
        "oXenon is a gas that is in the air we breathe (in very small amounts— 0.09 parts per "
        "million![2])\n\n"

        "oXenon gas is used in high quality light bulbs, including automobile headlamps and movie "
        "projectors.\n\n"

        "oThe most common propellant used in ion propulsion is xenon, which is easily ionized and "
        "has a high atomic mass, thus generating a desirable level of thrust when ions are "
        "accelerated.\n\n"

        "oIt also is inert and has a high storage density; therefore, it is well suited for "
        "storing on spacecraft.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_spacecraft">
        "Spacecraft size:\n"
        "•The full spacecraft, including the solar panels, is 24.76 meters (~81 feet) long by "
        "7.34 meters (~24 feet) wide.\n"
        "•That is about the size of a (singles) tennis court.\n\n"

        "Bus size:\n"
        "•The bus (body) of the spacecraft is 3.1 meters (~10 feet) long by 2.4 meters "
        "(almost 8 feet) wide.\n\n"

        "A few size comparisons:\n"
        "•It is slightly bigger than a Smart Car.\n"
        "•It about the size of a garden storage shed.\n"
        "•It is as tall as a regulation basketball hoop!\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_cost">
        "Mission cost:\n"
        "•Estimated $850 million (includes mission development, operations, and science)\n"
        "•Amount does not include cost for the launch service which is procured separately\n"
        "•Amount does not include the cost for the Deep Space Optical Communications demonstration "
        "hardware or operations\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_asteroid"><![CDATA[
        "Psyche, the Asteroid:\n\n"
        "• Discovered in 1852.\n"
        "• Discovered by Italian astronomer Annibale de Gasparis.\n"
        "• 16th asteroid to be discovered.\n"
        "• Named for the goddess of the soul in ancient Greek mythology.\n"
        "• Composition: Psyche is likely made almost entirely of nickel-iron metal.\n\n"

        "• Its bulk appears to be metal but its surface appears to have small areas that are rocky.\n"
        "o How do we know? Confirmed by measurements of:\n"
        "▪ Radar albedo: The “ratio of a target’s radar cross section in a specified polarization "
        "to its projected area; hence, a measure of the target’s radar reflectivity.”[4, 5])\n"

        "▪ Thermal inertia: “Refers to the ability of a material to conduct and store heat, and in "
        "planetary science, its measure of the subsurface's ability to store heat during the day "
        "and re-radiate it during the night.”[6])\n"

        "o When did we find out? We have only had good evidence for metal composition since "
        "about 2010.\n\n"

        "• Scientists believe Psyche is the exposed nickel-iron core of an early planet, one of "
        "the building blocks of our solar system.\n\n"

        "• Psyche is most likely a survivor of multiple violent hit-and-run collisions, common "
        "when the solar system was forming.\n\n"

        "• The asteroid Psyche may be able to tell us how Earth’s core and the cores of the "
        "other terrestrial (rocky) planets came to be. (The terrestrial planets are Mercury, "
        "Venus, Earth, and Mars.)\n\n"

        "o We can never go to the Earth’s core:\n"
        "▪ Earth’s core lies at 3,000 kilometers (more than 1,800 miles) depth but we have only "
        "drilled to 12 kilometers (~7.5 miles) – that’s the most our technology allows today.\n"
        "▪ Earth’s core lies at about 3 million times the pressure of the atmosphere\n"
        "▪ The temperature of Earth’s core is about 5,000 Celsius (~9,000 Fahrenheit)\n\n"

        "o Because we cannot see or measure Earth’s core directly, asteroid Psyche offers a "
        "unique window into the violent history of collisions and accretion that created the "
        "terrestrial planets.\n\n"

        "o It is the only known place in our solar system where we can examine directly what is "
        "almost certainly a metallic core of an early planet.\n\n"

        "• Psyche lies in the main asteroid belt between Mars and Jupiter.\n\n"

        "• A day on Psyche is about 4 hours and 12 minutes.[7]\n"
        "o This is the sidereal rotation period, or the "amount of time it takes for a [body] to completely spin around and make one full rotation."[8]\n"
        "o You could live through just under six “days” on Psyche in the same time as one day"
        "on Earth!\n\n"

        "• A year on Psyche lasts about five Earth years (about 1,828 Earth days)[9].\n\n"

        "• Psyche orbits the Sun at an average distance of 3 astronomical units (AU) "
        "(about 280 million miles); Earth orbits at 1 AU (about 93 million miles).\n\n"

        "o Fun fact: Because Psyche and Earth orbit at different speeds, the distance from Earth "
        "to Psyche varies over a large range! From < 2 AU to > 4 AU.\n\n"

        "• Density: Psyche is dense—perhaps as dense as 7,000 kilograms per cubic meter (kg/m3) "
        "(similar to the density of a bar of steel)[10].\n\n"

        "• Gravity: The surface gravity on Psyche is much less than Earth, and even less than the "
        "Moon. On Psyche, lifting a car would feel as light as lifting a dog or a 2nd grader!\n\n"

        "• Size: As asteroids go, Psyche is relatively large and has an irregular shape:\n"

        "o 279 x 232 x 189 kilometers (173 x 144 x 117 miles)[11].\n\n"
        "o If Psyche were a perfect sphere, it would have a diameter of 226 kilometers (140 miles):\n"

        "▪ That is about the length of the state of Massachusetts (leaving out Cape Cod); If it "
        "were in Arizona it would stretch between Phoenix and Flagstaff!\n\n"

        "▪ a surface area of about 641,800 square kilometers (246,300 square miles), making it just"
        "smaller than the area of the state of Texas and quite a bit larger than the area of "
        "California.\n\n"

        "• Appearance: Scientists have combined radar and optical observations to generate a "
        "3D shape model of Psyche[12]. This model:\n"
        "o Shows evidence for two crater-like depressions.\n"
        "o Suggests that there is significant variation in the metal content and color of the "
        "asteroid over the surface.\n"
        "o NOTE: No one has seen the Psyche asteroid yet, so we will not know what it actually "
        "looks like until the spacecraft arrives. This is the best look we have from radar "
        "observations: [Insert Picture here?]\n\n"
    ]]></string>
    <string name="faq_mission_science_goals">
        "Psyche Mission Science Goals:\n\n"
        "• Understand a previously unexplored building block of planet formation: iron cores.\n\n"
        
        "• Look inside terrestrial planets, including Earth, by directly examining the interior of "
        "a differentiated body, which otherwise could not be seen.\n\n"
        
        "• Explore a new type of world. For the first time, examine a world made not of rock and "
        "ice, but metal.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_science_objectives">
        "Psyche Mission Science Objectives\n\n"
        "• Determine whether Psyche is a core, or if it is unmelted material.\n\n"

        "• Determine the relative ages of regions of Psyche’s surface.\n\n"

        "• Determine whether small metal bodies incorporate the same light elements as are "
        "expected in the Earth’s high-pressure core.\n\n"

        "• Determine whether Psyche was formed under conditions more oxidizing or more reducing "
        "than Earth’s core.\n\n"

        "• Characterize Psyche’s morphology.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_instruments_and_investigations">
        "Psyche Mission Science Instruments and Investigations\n\n"

        "The Psyche Multispectral Imager:\n\n"
        "• Provides high-resolution images using filters to discriminate between Psyche’s metallic "
        "and silicate constituents.\n\n"

        "• Consists of a pair of identical cameras designed to acquire geologic, compositional, "
        "and topographic data.\n\n"

        "• Purpose of the second camera is to provide redundancy for mission-critical optical "
        "navigation.\n\n"

        "• The team is based at Arizona State University.\n\n"

        "The Psyche Gamma Ray and Neutron Spectrometer:\n\n"
        "• Will detect, measure, and map Psyche’s elemental composition.\n\n"
        "• Mounted on a 2-meter (6-foot) boom (“arm”) to:\n"
        "o distance the sensors from background radiation created by energetic particles "
        "interacting with the spacecraft;\n"
        "o provide an unobstructed field of view.\n\n"

        "• The team is based at the Applied Physics Laboratory at Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"

        "The Psyche Magnetometer\n\n"
        "• Designed to detect and measure the remnant magnetic field of the asteroid.\n\n"

        "• Composed of two identical high-sensitivity magnetic field sensors located at the "
        "middle and outer end of a 2-meter (6-foot) boom (&quot;arm&quot;).\n\n"

        "• The team is based at Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) and the University of "
        "California Los Angeles (UCLA).\n\n"

        "Radio Science:\n\n"
        "• The Psyche mission will use the X-band radio telecommunications system to measure "
        "Psyche’s gravity field to high precision.\n\n"

        "• When combined with topography derived from onboard imagery, this will provide "
        "information on the interior structure of Psyche.\n\n"

        "• The team is based at MIT and JPL.\n\n"

        "Deep Space Optical Communication (DSOC):\n\n"
        "• The Psyche mission will test a sophisticated new laser communication technology that "
        "encodes data in photons (rather than radio waves) to communicate between a probe in deep "
        "space and Earth.\n\n"

        "• Using light instead of radio allows the spacecraft to communicate more data in a given "
        "amount of time.\n\n"

        "• The DSOC team is based at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_team">
        "Psyche Mission Team\n\n"
        "Principal Investigator (PI): Lindy Elkins-Tanton, Arizona State University (ASU)\n"
        "• The PI is responsible for overall mission success, and for the scientific integrity and "
        "execution of the mission within committed cost and schedule.\n\n"

        "• The PI oversees the team organization, decides science priorities and progress, and "
        "oversees delivery of mission data to NASA’s Planetary Data System.\n\n"

        "• The PI is the decision-maker within the Psyche team, and NASA is the ultimate "
        "decision-maker.\n\n"

        "• The PI is responsible for ensuring that all mission participants are playing their roles "
        "as defined by the Team Guidelines.\n\n"

        "Deputy Principal Investigator (Deputy PI): Jim Bell, ASU\n\n"

        "Co-Investigators:\n
        "• Erik Asphaug, University of Arizona\n"
        "• David Bercovici, Yale University\n
        "• Bruce Bills, Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)\n"
        "• Richard Binzel, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)\n"
        "• William Bottke, Southwest Research Institute (SwRI)\n"
        "• Ralf Jaumann, Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt\n"
        "• Insoo Jun, JPL\n"
        "• David Lawrence, Johns Hopkins University, Applied Physics Laboratory (APL)\n"
        "• Simone Marchi, SwRI\n"
        "• Timothy McCoy, Smithsonian Institution\n"
        "• Ryan Park, JPL\n"
        "• Patrick Peplowski, APL\n"
        "• Thomas Prettyman, Planetary Science Institute\n"
        "• Carol Raymond, JPL\n"
        "• Chris Russell, University of California, Los Angeles\n"
        "• Benjamin Weiss, MIT\n"
        "• Dan Wenkert, JPL\n"
        "• Mark Wieczorek, Observatoire de la Côte d’Azur\n"
        "• David Williams, ASU\n"
        "• Maria Zuber, MIT\n\n"

        "Psyche Science Partners:\n"
        "• Applied Physics Laboratory (APL)\n"
        "• Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt (DLR)\n"
        "• General Dynamics\n"
        "• Glenn Research Center (GRC)\n"
        "• Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)\n"
        "• Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)\n"
        "• Malin Space Science Systems (MSSS)\n"
        "• Observatoire de la Côte d’Azur\n"
        "• Planetary Science Institute (PSI)\n"
        "• Smithsonian Institution\n"
        "• Southwest Research Institute (SwRI)\n"
        "• SSL\n"
        "• Tesat Spacecom\n"
        "• University of Arizona\n"
        "• University of California Los Angeles (UCLA)\n"
        "• Yale University\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_more_info">
        "The mission is led by Arizona State University. NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory is "
        "responsible for mission management, operations and navigation. The spacecraft’s "
        "solar-electric propulsion chassis will be built by SSL with a payload that includes an "
        "imager, magnetometer, and a gamma-ray spectrometer.\n\n"

        "Want to learn more about Psyche?\n\n"
        "Visit:\n"
        "sese.asu.edu/Psyche \n"
        "www.jpl.nasa.gov/missions/psyche \n"
        "www.nasa.gov/psyche \n\n"

        "Social Media:\n"
        "Twitter: @NASAPsyche\n"
        "Facebook: NASAPsyche\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_references">
        "References:\n\n"

        "[1] https://www.nasa.gov/content/how-will-nasas-asteroid-redirect-mission-help-humans-reach-mars\n\n"

        "[2] http://www.srh.noaa.gov/jetstream/atmos/atmos_intro.html\n\n"

        "[3] https://www.nasa.gov/centers/glenn/about/fs21grc.html\n\n"

        "[4] Ostro, S. J. (1999). Planetary Radar. Encyclopedia of the Solar System. Available "
        "from http://echo.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroids/ostro_1998_encyc_ss.pdf\n\n"

        "[5] Radar is an acronym for &quot;radio detection and ranging.&quot; Radar was developed to "
        "detect objects and determine their range (or position) by transmitting short bursts of "
        "microwaves. The strength and origin of "echoes" received from objects that were "
        "hit by the microwaves is then recorded.\n\n"

        "[6] https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/spaceimages/details.php?id=PIA19357\n\n"

        "[7] Shepard, M. K., Richardson, J., Taylor, P. A., Rodriguez-Ford, L. A., Conrad, A., "
        "de Pater, I., … &amp; Close, L. M. (2017). Radar observations and shape model of asteroid "
        "16 Psyche. Icarus, 281, 388-403: "sidereal rotation period P = 4.195948 h" \n\n"

        "[8] https://spaceplace.nasa.gov/days/en/ \n\n"

        "[9] https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=16 \n\n"

        "[10] Elkins-Tanton, L. T., Asphaug, E., Bell, J. F., Bercovici, D., Bills, B. G., "
        "Binzel, R. P., … &amp; Jun, I. (2017, March). Asteroid (16) Psyche: Visiting a Metal World. "
        "In Lunar and Planetary Science Conference (Vol. 48).\n\n"

        "[11] Shepard, M. K., Richardson, J., Taylor, P. A., Rodriguez-Ford, L. A., Conrad, A., "
        "de Pater, I., … &amp; Close, L. M. (2017). Radar observations and shape model of asteroid "
        "16 Psyche. Icarus, 281, 388-403.\n\n"

        "[12] http://outreach.naic.edu/ao/blog/radar-observations-and-shape-model-asteroid-16-psyche\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>