<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="faq_options">
        <item>Intro</item>
        <item>Timeline Summary</item>
        <item>Psyche the Asteroid</item>
        <item>Spacecraft</item>
        <item>Propulsion</item>
        <item>Mission Cost</item>
        <item>Mission Science Goals</item>
        <item>Mission Science Objectives</item>
        <item>Instruments and Investigations</item>
        <item>Psyche Mission Team</item>
        <item>More Information</item>
        <item>References</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="faq_array">
        <item>@string/faq_intro</item>
        <item>@string/faq_timeline_summary</item>
        <item>@string/faq_asteroid</item>
        <item>@string/faq_spacecraft</item>
        <item>@string/faq_propulsion</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_cost</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_science_goals</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_science_objectives</item>
        <item>@string/faq_instruments_and_investigations</item>
        <item>@string/faq_mission_team</item>
        <item>@string/faq_more_info</item>
        <item>@string/faq_references</item>
    </array>
    <string name="faq_intro">
        <b>"What is Psyche?</b>"
        "\nPsyche is the name of an asteroid orbiting the Sun between Mars and Jupiter and "
        "the name of a NASA space mission to visit that asteroid, led by ASU. Psyche is "
        "the first mission to a world made of metal rather than rock or ice.\n"

        "<b>\nWhen was the Psyche mission selected?</b>"
        "\nThe Psyche mission was chosen by NASA on January 4, 2017.\n"

        "<b>\nWhat kind of mission is Psyche?</b>"
        "\nPsyche is the 14th mission selected for NASA’s Discovery Program, a series of "
        "relatively low-cost missions to solar system targets."
    </string>
    <string name="faq_timeline_summary">
        "<b>What is the timeline of the Psyche mission?</b>"

        "\n• 2022: Launch of Psyche spacecraft from NASA’s Kennedy Space Center, FL"

        "\n• 2023: Psyche spacecraft flyby of Mars"

        "\n• 2026: Psyche spacecraft arrives in asteroid’s orbit"

        "\n• 2026 - 2027: Psyche spacecraft orbits the Psyche asteroid for 21 months\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_propulsion">
        "<b>How will the Psyche spacecraft get to Psyche?</b>"
        "\nThe Psyche spacecraft will use solar-electric (low-thrust) propulsion. Solar electric "
        "propulsion uses electricity from solar arrays to create electromagnetic fields to accelerate "
        "and expel charged atoms (ions) of xenon to create a very low thrust with a very efficient "
        "use of propellant[1]. This will be the first use of Hall effect thrusters beyond lunar orbit."

        "\n\n<b>What kind of propellant will the Psyche spacecraft use?</b>"
        "\nThe Psyche spacecraft is using xenon. Xenon is a gas that is in the air we "
        "breathe (in very small amounts— 0.09 parts per million![2]). Xenon gas is used in high "
        "quality light bulbs, including automobile headlamps and movie projectors. "
        "As NASA explains, “The most common propellant used in ion propulsion is xenon, which is easily "
        "ionized and has a high atomic mass, thus generating a desirable level of thrust when ions "
        "are accelerated. It also is inert and has a high storage density; therefore, it is well "
        "suited for storing on spacecraft.”[3]\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_spacecraft">
        "<b>How big will the Psyche spacecraft be?</b>"
        "\nThe full spacecraft, including the solar panels, is 24.76 meters (~81 feet) long by 7.34 meters (~24 feet) wide. "
        "That is about the size of a (singles) tennis court."

        "\n\n<b>How big will the Psyche spacecraft bus (body) be?</b>"
        "\nThe bus (body) of the spacecraft is 3.1 meters (~10 feet) long by 2.4 meters (almost 8 feet) wide. "
        "To help you visualize this, it is slightly bigger than a Smart Car; "
        "it about the size of a garden storage shed. It is as tall as a regulation basketball hoop!"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_cost">
        "<b>How much does the Psyche mission cost?</b>"
        "\nThe mission costs approximately $850 million (which includes mission development, operations, and science). "
        "This amount does not include cost for the launch service, which is procured separately. "
        "It does not include the cost for the Deep Space Optical Communications demonstration hardware or operations."
    </string>
    <string name="faq_asteroid">
        "<b>When was the Psyche asteroid discovered?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[The asteroid, Psyche, was discovered in 1852 by Italian astronomer Annibale de Gasparis. "
        "It was the 16th asteroid to be discovered, so is sometimes referred to as (16) Psyche. "
        "The asteroid was named for the goddess of the soul in ancient Greek mythology."]]>

        "\n\n<b>What is the Psyche asteroid made of?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[Psyche is likely made almost entirely of nickel-iron metal. Its bulk appears to be metal"
        "but its surface appears to have small areas that are rocky."]]>

        "\n\n<b>How do we know what the Psyche asteroid is made of?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[The composition of Psyche has been determined by radar albedo (radar albedo is "
        "the “ratio of a target’s radar cross section in a specified polarization to its projected area; "
        "hence, a measure of the target’s radar reflectivity”[4],[5]) and by thermal inertia "
        "(thermal inertia “refers to the ability of a material to conduct and store heat, and in planetary "
        "science, its measure of the subsurface's ability to store heat during the day and re-radiate it during the night.”[6])"]]>

        "\n\n<b>When did we find out what Psyche is made of?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[We have only had good evidence for metal composition since about 2010."]]>

        "\n\n<b>What do scientists think the Psyche asteroid is?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[Scientists think Psyche is the exposed nickel-iron core of an early planet, one of the "
        "building blocks of our solar system.  Psyche is most likely a survivor of multiple violent "
        "hit-and-run collisions, common when the solar system was forming."]]>

        "\n\n<b>What can visiting the Psyche asteroid tell us?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[The asteroid Psyche may be able to tell us how Earth’s core and the cores of the other "
        "terrestrial (rocky) planets came to be. (The terrestrial planets are Mercury, Venus, Earth, and Mars.) "
        "We can never go to the Earth’s core. Because we cannot see or measure Earth’s core "
        "directly, the Psyche asteroid offers a unique window into the violent history of collisions "
        "and accretion that created the terrestrial planets. It is the only known place in our solar "
        "system where we can examine directly what is almost certainly a metallic core of an early planet."]]>

        "\n\n<b>Why can’t we visit Earth’s core?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[The core of the Earth lies at a depth of 3,000 kilometers, or more than 1,800 miles. "
        "We have only drilled to 12 kilometers, or about 7.5 miles, so far because that’s the most "
        "our technology allows today. Additionally, Earth’s core lies at about 3 million times the "
        "pressure of the atmosphere. The temperature of Earth’s core is about 5,000 Celsius (~9,000 Fahrenheit)."]]>

        "\n\n<b>Where is the Psyche asteroid?</b>"
        "\nPsyche lies in the main asteroid belt between Mars and Jupiter."

        "\n\n<b>How long is a day on Psyche?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[A day on Psyche is about 4 hours and 12 minutes.[7] This is the sidereal rotation period, or the "amount of time it takes for a [body] to completely spin around and make one full rotation."[8] You could live through just under six “days” on Psyche in the same time as one day on Earth!"]]>

        "\n\n<b>How long is a year on Psyche?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[A year on Psyche lasts about five Earth years (about 1,828 Earth days).[9]"]]>

        "\n\n<b>How far is the Psyche asteroid from the Sun?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[Psyche orbits the Sun at an average distance of 3 astronomical units (AU) (about 280 million miles); "
        "Earth orbits at 1 AU (about 93 million miles). Because Psyche and Earth orbit at different speeds, "
        "the distance from Earth to Psyche varies over a large range! From < 2 AU to > 4 AU."]]>

        "\n\n<b>How dense is the Psyche asteroid?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[Psyche is dense—perhaps as dense as 7,000 kilograms per cubic meter (kg/m3) (similar to the density of a bar of steel).[10]"]]>

        "\n\n<b>Does the Psyche asteroid have gravity?</b>"
        "\nThe surface gravity on Psyche is much less than Earth, and even less than the Moon. On Psyche, "
        "lifting a car would feel as light as lifting a dog or a 2nd grader!"

        "\n\n<b>How big is the Psyche asteroid?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[As asteroids go, Psyche is relatively large and has an irregular shape. "
        "It is 279 x 232 x 189 kilometers (173 x 144 x 117 miles).[11]  If Psyche were a perfect sphere, "
        "it would have a diameter of 226 kilometers (140 miles). That is about the length of the "
        "state of Massachusetts (leaving out Cape Cod). If it were in Arizona it would stretch between "
        "Phoenix and Flagstaff!  The Psyche asteroid has a surface area of about 641,800 square kilometers (246,300 square miles), "
        "making it just smaller than the area of the state of Texas and quite a bit larger than the area of California."]]>

        "\n\n<b>What does the Psyche asteroid look like?</b>"
        "\n<![CDATA[Scientists have combined radar and optical observations to generate a 3D shape model of Psyche.[12] "
        "This model shows evidence for two crater-like depressions. It suggests that there is significant "
        "variation in the metal content and color of the asteroid over the surface. But remember, no one "
        "has seen the Psyche asteroid yet, so we will not know what it actually looks like until the "
        "spacecraft arrives."]]>
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_science_goals">
        "<b>What are the Psyche mission science goals?</b>"
        "\n\nThe Psyche mission science goals are to:"
        "\n• Understand a previously unexplored building block of planet formation: iron cores."
        "\n• Look inside terrestrial planets, including Earth, by directly examining the interior of a differentiated body, which otherwise could not be seen."
        "\n• Explore a new type of world. For the first time, examine a world made not of rock and ice, but metal."
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_science_objectives">
        "<b>What are the Psyche mission science objectives?</b>"
        "\n\nThe Psyche mission science objectives are to:"
        "\n• Determine whether Psyche is a core, or if it is unmelted material."
        "\n• Determine the relative ages of regions of Psyche’s surface."
        "\n• Determine whether small metal bodies incorporate the same light elements as are expected in the Earth’s high-pressure core."
        "\n• Determine whether Psyche was formed under conditions more oxidizing or more reducing than Earth’s core."
        "\n• Characterize Psyche’s morphology.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_instruments_and_investigations">
        "<b>What instruments are on the Psyche mission?</b>"
        "\nThe Psyche spacecraft will carry a multispectral imager, a gamma ray and neutron spectrometer, "
        "and a magnetometer, and will conduct radio science."

        "\n\n<b>Facts about the Psyche Multispectral Imager:</b>"
        "\n• Provides high-resolution images using filters to discriminate between Psyche’s metallic and silicate constituents."
        "\n• Consists of a pair of identical cameras designed to acquire geologic, compositional, and topographic data."
        "\n• Purpose of the second camera is to provide redundancy for mission-critical optical navigation."
        "\n• The team is based at Arizona State University."

        "\n\n<b>Facts about the Psyche Gamma Ray and Neutron Spectrometer:</b>"
        "\n• Will detect, measure, and map Psyche’s elemental composition."
        "\n• Mounted on a 2-meter (6-foot) boom (“arm”) to:"
        "\n\t\t\t\to distance the sensors from background radiation created by energetic particles interacting with the spacecraft;"
        "\n\t\t\t\to provide an unobstructed field of view."
        "\n• The team is based at the Applied Physics Laboratory at Johns Hopkins University."

        "\n\n<b>Facts about the Psyche Magnetometer:</b>"
        "\n• Designed to detect and measure the remnant magnetic field of the asteroid."
        "\n• Composed of two identical high-sensitivity magnetic field sensors located at the middle and "
        "outer end of a 2-meter (6-foot) boom (“arm”)."
        "\n• The team is based at Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) and the University of California Los Angeles (UCLA)."

        "\n\n<b>Facts about Psyche Radio Science:</b>"
        "\n• The Psyche mission will use the X-band radio telecommunications system to measure Psyche’s gravity field to high precision."
        "\n• When combined with topography derived from onboard imagery, this will provide information on the interior structure of Psyche."
        "\n• The team is based at MIT and JPL."

        "\n\n<b>Facts about the Deep Space Optical Communication (DSOC):</b>"
        "\n• The Psyche mission will test a sophisticated new laser communication technology that encodes "
        "data in photons (rather than radio waves) to communicate between a probe in deep space and Earth."
        "\n• Using light instead of radio allows the spacecraft to communicate more data in a given amount of time."
        "\n• The DSOC team is based at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_mission_team">
        "<b>Who is on the Psyche mission team?</b>"
        "\nThe Principal Investigator is Lindy Elkins-Tanton, Arizona State University (ASU) and the "
        "Deputy Principal Investigator is Jim Bell, ASU.  Other co-investigators are:"
        "\n• Erik Asphaug, University of Arizona"
        "\n• David Bercovici, Yale University"
        "\n• Bruce Bills, Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)"
        "\n• Richard Binzel, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)"
        "\n• William Bottke, Southwest Research Institute (SwRI)"
        "\n• Catherine Bowman, ASU • Ralf Jaumann, Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt"
        "\n• Insoo Jun, JPL"
        "\n• David Lawrence, Johns Hopkins University, Applied Physics Laboratory (APL)"
        "\n• Simone Marchi, SwRI"
        "\n• Timothy McCoy, Smithsonian Institution"
        "\n• Ryan Park, JPL"
        "\n• Patrick Peplowski, APL"
        "\n• Carol Polansky, JPL"
        "\n• Thomas Prettyman, Planetary Science Institute"
        "\n• Carol Raymond, JPL"
        "\n• Chris Russell, University of California, Los Angeles"
        "\n• Benjamin Weiss, MIT"
        "\n• Dan Wenkert, JPL"
        "\n• Mark Wieczorek, Observatoire de la Côte d’Azur"
        "\n• David Williams, ASU"
        "\n• Maria Zuber, MIT"

        "\n\n<b>The Mission leadership includes:</b>"
        "\n• Diane Brown, Program Executive, NASA Headquarters (HQ)"
        "\n• Sarah Noble, Program Scientist, NASA HQ"
        "\n• Belinda Wright, Mission Manager, NASA Marshall Space Flight Center (MSFC)"
        "\n• Henry Stone, Project Manager, JPL"
        "\n• Robert Mase, Deputy Project Manager and Acting Mission System Manager, JPL"
        "\n• Brian Johnson, Project Business Manager, JPL"
        "\n• David Oh, Project System Engineer, JPL"
        "\n• Kalyani Sukhatme, Payload Manager, JPL"
        "\n• Rob Menke, Mission Assurance Manager, JPL"
        "\n• Mark Brown, Flight System Manager, JPL"
        "\n• Steve Schott, SEP Chassis Program Manager, SSL"
        "\n• Peter Lord, SEP Chassis Deputy Program Manager, SSL"

        "\n\n<b>What does the Principal Investigator (PI) do?</b>"
        "\n• The PI is responsible for overall mission success, and for the scientific integrity and "
        "execution of the mission within committed cost and schedule."
        "\n• The PI oversees the team organization, decides science priorities and progress, and oversees "
        "delivery of mission data to NASA’s Planetary Data System."
        "\n• The PI is the decision-maker within the Psyche team, and NASA is the ultimate decision-maker."
        "\n• The PI is responsible for ensuring that all mission participants are playing their roles as defined by the Team Guidelines."

        "\n\n<b>Who are the Psyche science partners?</b>"
        "\nThe Psyche science partners are:"
        "\n• Applied Physics Laboratory (APL)"
        "\n• Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt (DLR)"
        "\n• Glenn Research Center (GRC)"
        "\n• Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)"
        "\n• Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)"
        "\n• Malin Space Science Systems (MSSS)"
        "\n• Observatoire de la Côte d’Azur"
        "\n• Planetary Science Institute (PSI)"
        "\n• Smithsonian Institution"
        "\n• Southwest Research Institute (SwRI)"
        "\n• SSL"
        "\n• University of Arizona"
        "\n• University of California Los Angeles (UCLA)"
        "\n• Yale University"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_more_info">
        "<b>Who is building the Psyche mission?</b>"
        "\nThe mission is led by Arizona State University. NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory is responsible "
        "for mission management, operations and navigation. The spacecraft’s solar-electric propulsion "
        "chassis will be built by SSL with a payload that includes an imager, magnetometer, and a gamma-ray spectrometer."

        "\n\n<b>How can I learn more about the Psyche mission?</b>"
        "\nTo learn more about the Psyche mission, visit:"
        "\nsese.asu.edu/Psyche"
        "\nwww.jpl.nasa.gov/missions/psyche"
        "\nwww.nasa.gov/psyche"
        "\n\nOr follow the Psyche mission on social media:"
        "\nTwitter: @NASAPsyche"
        "\nFacebook: NASAPsyche"
        "\nInstagram: @nasapsyche"
    </string>
    <string name="faq_references">
        "References:\n\n"

        "[1] https://www.nasa.gov/content/how-will-nasas-asteroid-redirect-mission-help-humans-reach-mars\n\n"

        "[2] http://www.srh.noaa.gov/jetstream/atmos/atmos_intro.html\n\n"

        "[3] https://www.nasa.gov/centers/glenn/about/fs21grc.html\n\n"

        "[4] Ostro, S. J. (1999). Planetary Radar. Encyclopedia of the Solar System. Available "
        "from http://echo.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroids/ostro_1998_encyc_ss.pdf\n\n"

        "[5] Radar is an acronym for &quot;radio detection and ranging.&quot; Radar was developed to "
        "detect objects and determine their range (or position) by transmitting short bursts of "
        "microwaves. The strength and origin of "echoes" received from objects that were "
        "hit by the microwaves is then recorded.\n\n"

        "[6] https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/spaceimages/details.php?id=PIA19357\n\n"

        "[7] Shepard, M. K., Richardson, J., Taylor, P. A., Rodriguez-Ford, L. A., Conrad, A., "
        "de Pater, I., … &amp; Close, L. M. (2017). Radar observations and shape model of asteroid "
        "16 Psyche. Icarus, 281, 388-403: "sidereal rotation period P = 4.195948 h" \n\n"

        "[8] https://spaceplace.nasa.gov/days/en/ \n\n"

        "[9] https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=16 \n\n"

        "[10] Elkins-Tanton, L. T., Asphaug, E., Bell, J. F., Bercovici, D., Bills, B. G., "
        "Binzel, R. P., … &amp; Jun, I. (2017, March). Asteroid (16) Psyche: Visiting a Metal World. "
        "In Lunar and Planetary Science Conference (Vol. 48).\n\n"

        "[11] Shepard, M. K., Richardson, J., Taylor, P. A., Rodriguez-Ford, L. A., Conrad, A., "
        "de Pater, I., … &amp; Close, L. M. (2017). Radar observations and shape model of asteroid "
        "16 Psyche. Icarus, 281, 388-403.\n\n"

        "[12] http://outreach.naic.edu/ao/blog/radar-observations-and-shape-model-asteroid-16-psyche\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>
