<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Intro">
        "Psyche is:\n\n"

        "\t-The name of an asteroid orbiting the Sun between Mars and Jupiter.\n"
        "\t-The name of an ASU space mission to visit that asteroid.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Fact_1">Psyche is the first mission to a world made of metal rather than rock or ice.</string>
    <string name="Fact_2">The Psyche mission was chosen by NASA on January 4, 2017.</string>
    <string name="Fact_3">
        "Psyche is the 14th mission selected for NASA’s Discovery Program, "
        "a series of relatively low-cost missions to solar system targets.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Timeline_Facts">
        "Summary of Psyche Mission Timeline:\n\n"

        "\t2022: Launch of Psyche spacecraft from NASA’s Kennedy Space Center, FL\n"
        "\t2023: Psyche spacecraft flyby of Mars\n"
        "\t2026: Psyche spacecraft arrives in asteroid’s orbit\n"
        "\t2026-2027: Psyche spacecraft orbits the Psyche asteroid for 21 months\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Propulsion_Facts">
        "Propulsion: Solar-electric (low-thrust) propulsion.\n\n"

        "Solar electric propulsion uses electricity from solar arrays to create electromagnetic fields to accelerate and expel charged atoms (ions) of xenon to create a very low thrust with a very efficient use of propellant[1].\n"
        "This will be the first use of Hall effect thrusters beyond lunar orbit.\n"

        "The Psyche spacecraft is using xenon:\n"
        "\t-Xenon is a gas that is in the air we breathe (in very small amounts— 0.09 parts per million![2])\n"
        "\t-Xenon gas is used in high quality light bulbs, including automobile headlamps and movie projectors.\n"
        “\t-The most common propellant used in ion propulsion is xenon, "
        "which is easily ionized and has a high atomic mass, "
        "thus generating a desirable level of thrust when ions are accelerated. "
        "It also is inert and has a high storage density; therefore, it is well suited for storing on spacecraft.\n"
    </string>
</resources>
