<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <integer-array name="image_thumbnails">
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_sgarcia_project3_manyminds_180221_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_ksanford_project5_wordcloud_180328_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_aweibel_project4_psycheinspiredportraits_180327_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_nbacalzo_anorenberg_project4_psychepop_up_180323_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_cvasquez_project5_heavymetallightshow_180321_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_aweibel_project3_psychecrossstitch_180319_640x420</item>
        <item>@drawable/gallery_thumb_nbacalzo_project4_psychestopmotion_180316_640x420</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="image_urls">
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_SGarcia_Project4_PsycheComic_180402-791x1024.jpg</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_KSanford_Project5_WordCloud_180328-1024x791.png</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_AWeibel_Project4_PsycheInspiredPortraits_180327-906x1024.jpg</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_NBacalzo_ANorenberg_Project4_PsychePop-Up_180323-1024x656.jpg</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_CVasquez_Project5_HeavyMetalLightShow_180321.jpg</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_AWeibel_Project3_PsycheCrossStitch_180319-1024x683.jpg</item>
        <item>https://psyche.asu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Psyche_Inspired_17-18_NBacalzo_Project4_PsycheStopMotion_180316.png</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="image_description_array">
        <item>@string/psyche_comic</item>
        <item>@string/psyche_word_cloud</item>
        <item>@string/psyche_inspired_intern_portraits</item>
        <item>@string/psyche_pop_up_book</item>
        <item>@string/heavy_metal_light_show</item>
        <item>@string/cross_stitch</item>
        <item>@string/stop_motion</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="backyard_telescope">
        "Artist: Caralie Cedarleaf"
        "\nDate: April 3, 2018"
        "\nMajor: sculpture"
        "\nGenre/Medium: cast iron, acrylic, LEDs, copper wire, dichroic film, aluminum ducting"
        "\n\nAbout the work: Backyard Telescope represents the accessibility of the asteroid (16) Psyche to scientists and non-scientists alike because of the Psyche Mission. Images and information collected during NASA-led missions are made available as part of the public domain, allowing amateur astronomers a chance to learn about space. This diorama returns to a childlike fascination with exploration and learning."
        "\n\nThe asteroid in the center is cast in iron, an element in Psyche’s composition. The laser cut Psyche spacecraft orbits the asteroid on a copper wire, referencing Arizona’s role in the mission. The star patterns are designed after sculptures of the goddess Psyche from the era of the asteroid’s discovery. The dichroic film – which was developed in the late 1950s by NASA and the Department of Defense to protect sensitive instruments from cosmic radiation and to shield astronauts’ vision from unfiltered sunlight – represents the decades of great scientists and engineers who have made and continue to make space exploration possible."
    </string>
    <string name="psyche_comic">
        "Artist: Sofia Garcia"
        "\nDate: April 2, 2018"
        "\nMajor: painting"
        "\nGenre/Medium: digital illustration"
        "\n\nAbout the work: This work is a fictional story of the development of Psyche. A friendship between a human and a spacecraft, discovering what is beyond the metal world."
    </string>
    <string name="psyche_word_cloud">
        "Artist: Kari Sanford"
        "\nDate: March 28, 2018"
        "\nMajor: engineering management"
        "\nGenre/Medium: word cloud"
        "\n\nAbout the work: I wanted to tell the stories of the minds and hearts behind the Psyche Mission. With the team’s help, I approached scientists, engineers, journalists, and students associated with this mission and solicited their feedback. All of the words/phrases in this word cloud are their own. The most frequent, and inspiring, feedback that I saw was, ‘More than me,’ or ‘Bigger than me.’ This mission has helped people look beyond their own skillset and find ways to help others grow. Psyche has created a community through engagement: we are all connected through our pursuit of knowledge in deep space."
        "\n\nSpecial thanks to the contributors: Rona Oran | Steven Dibb | William Bottke | Tess Calvert | Dave Williams | Lindy Elkins-Tanton | Tim McCoy | Hannah L Bercovici | Brooke Owen | Mark Wieczorek | Sofia Garcia | Abigail Weibel | Karin Valentine | Erick Ramirez Cordero | Makenzie Kundrat | John Christoph | Stone Woodham | Brendan Scobie | Rachael Tjahjo | Isaac Wisdom"
    </string>
    <string name="psyche_inspired_intern_portraits">
        "Artist: Abigail Weibel"
        "\nDate: March 27, 2018"
        "\nMajor: geology"
        "\nGenre/Medium: photography"
        "\n\nAbout the work: Headshots of (most of) the inaugural Psyche Inspired interns taken for the Psyche website. (My headshot was taken by Brooke Owen, the Psyche Inspired student manager.)"
    </string>
    <string name="psyche_pop_up_book">
        "Artists: Nikka Bacalzo and Anne Norenberg"
        "\nDate: March 23, 2018"
        "\nMajor: graphic design (Nikka); digital culture (Anne)"
        "\nGenre/Medium: paper art and graphics"
        "\n\nAbout the work: This informative book was a collaboration between Nikka Bacalzo and Annie Norenberg. Annie designed the pages of the book and Nikka elevated the pictures with foam core as well as added the pull-tabs and pop-ups with cardstock, cut with an X-Acto. The book outlines a little history of Psyche, its instruments, the launch date and the purpose of the mission. Dimensions are ~8″ x 7″."
    </string>
    <string name="heavy_metal_light_show">
        "Artist: Chris Vasquez"
        "\nDate: March 21, 2018"
        "\nMajor: drawing"
        "\nGenre/Medium: wire and LED string lights"
        "\n\nAbout the work: With Psyche, you never have to take down your holiday lights! Inspired by festive holiday light sculptures, I wanted to create something reminiscent of those while keeping true to the design of Psyche."
    </string>
    <string name="cross_stitch">
        "Artist: Abigail Weibel"
        "\nDate: March 19, 2018"
        "\nMajor: geology"
        "\nGenre/Medium: cloth and thread, 8\" x 10\""
        "About the work: This cross stitch is based off the current artist rendering of the Psyche asteroid. I chose to exaggerate the image by using a lot of color to help it pop off the black background (and because there are only so many choices of grey thread!). If you are interested in cross-stitching your own Psyche, the pattern I created and thread color recommendations can be downloaded"
    </string>
    <string name="stop_motion">
        ""
    </string>
</resources>