<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="timeline_title">Psyche Mission Timeline</string>
    <string name="timeline_load">Loading Timeline…</string>
    <string name="timeline_past_info">
        "1852: Asteroid discovered by Italian astronomer Annibale de Gasparis\n\n"
        "2010: Composition of asteroid Psyche discovered to be all metal\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="timeline_future_info">
        "2022: Launch of Psyche spacecraft from NASA’s Kennedy Space Center, FL\n\n"
        "2023: Psyche spacecraft flyby of Mars\n\n"
        "2026: Psyche spacecraft arrives in asteroid’s orbit\n\n"
        "2026-2027: Psyche spacecraft orbits the Psyche asteroid for 21 months\n\n"
    </string>
    <string-array name="phase_letters">
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>D</item>
        <item>E</item>
        <item>F</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_titles">
        <item>Phase A: CONCEPT STUDY</item>
        <item>Phase B: PRELIMINARY DESIGN OF ALL INSTRUMENTS AND SPACECRAFT</item>
        <item>Phase C: CRITICAL DESIGN AND BUILD</item>
        <item>Phase D: INSTRUMENT AND SPACECRAFT BUILD, SHIP AND LAUNCH</item>
        <item>Phase E: GRAVITY ASSIST, ARRIVAL AND ORBIT</item>
        <item>Phase F: MISSION CLOSEOUT</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_A_info">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_A_summary">
        <item>1852: Asteroid discovered by Italian astronomer Annibale de Gasparis</item>
        <item>2010: Composition of asteroid Psyche discovered to be all metal</item>
        <item>September 2015: Psyche Mission selected for NASA concept study</item>
        <item>Details about Concept Study</item>
        <item>November 2016: Presentation for NASA\'s Discovery Program</item>
        <item>Details about NASA on-site Presentation</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_A_details">
        <item>
            "1852: Asteroid discovered by Italian astronomer Annibale de Gasparis\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "2010: Composition of asteroid Psyche discovered to be all metal\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "In September of 2015, the Psyche Mission (as it was proposed in Step 1) was selected "
            "by NASA to develop a detailed concept study for consideration for NASA\’s "
            "Discovery Program.\n\n"
            "Step 1 is the initial proposal stage; the team had been working on the idea "
            "since 2011 and submitted a 256 page Step 1 proposal that was selected for the "
            "Phase A concept study.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "A large team worked on the study, led by the Principal Investigator, "
            "Lindy Elkins-Tanton, and consisting of an expansive team that included scientists, "
            "engineers, project managers, schedulers, financial modelers, graphic designers, "
            "and marketing leads from ASU, JPL, SSL, as well as more than a dozen other "
            "universities and research organizations.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "In November of 2016, the team presented the proposed mission to 30 NASA reviewers "
            "during a nine-hour \“site visit\” which included a tour of SSL\’s high bay, "
            "where the Psyche chassis will be built.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "The site visit is an intense, highly technical in-person review done by a select "
            "group of science, technical, and industry experts. They review every detail of the "
            "proposed mission, from concept and design, to execution and science application, "
            "as well as how the mission personnel from different institutions work together "
            "as a team.\n\n"
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_B_summary">
        <item>January 2017: Science and engineering teams</item>
        <item>March 2019: Preliminary Design Review</item>
        <item>May 2019: Key Decision Point C</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_B_details">
        <item>
            "Science and engineering teams on the mission are designing the spacecraft and the instruments that will be used to analyze the asteroid.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "March 2019, the team will undergo project and flight system Preliminary Design Review.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "May 2019, the team reaches Key Decision Point C, which will give the team the official approval to move to the next phase (Phase C).\n\n"
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_C_summary">
        <item>May 2019: Science and engineering teams begin to build</item>
        <item>April 2020: Project and Flight System Critical Design Review</item>
        <item>May 2020: Spacecraft body completion</item>
        <item>January 2021: Systems Integration Review</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_C_details">
        <item>
            "Science and engineering teams begin to build their instruments.\n\n"
            "The instruments consist of a magnetometer, a multispectral imager, and a gamma ray and neutron spectrometer.\n\n"
            "The mission will use an X-band radio telecommunications system to measure Psyche\’s gravity field to high precision. When combined with topography derived from onboard imagery, this will provide information on the interior structure of Psyche.\n\n"
            "The mission will also test a sophisticated new laser communication technology that encodes data in photons (rather than radio waves) to communicate between a probe in deep space and Earth. Using light instead of radio allows the spacecraft to communicate more data in a given amount of time.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "April 2020, the teams will undergo Project and Flight System Critical Design Review, this is an integral step in the instrument engineering process.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "The bus or \“body\” of the spacecraft will be completed by May 2020.\n\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            "In January 2021, the team will conduct the Systems Integration Review to ensure that the system is ready to be integrated. The last step in Phase C is Key Decision Point D that will give the team the official approval to move to the next phase.\n\n"
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phase_D_summary">
        <item>DDD</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>